

(naukri.com®



Sateesh Kumar Ch.

Senior Software Engineer seeking roles in OBIEE, OLAP, Data Modelling, Tableau

Current Designation: Lead Consultant
Current Company: Apps Associates
Current Location: Hyderabad / Secunderabad
Pref. Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore, Chennai, Hyderabad
Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming / Maintenance
Role: Team Lead/Tech Lead
Industry: IT-Software/Software Services
Marital Status: Married

Last Active: 22-Jan-21 Last Modified: 22-Jan-21

Verified : Le Phone Number | Email - id

Jump to Section

Work Experience | Education | IT Skills |

### **Summary**

Achievement-driven professional with an experience of nearly 9 years

Impressive success in managing stakeholders throughout the project lifecycle while addressing priorities (time, budget/cost and resources) to attain delivery excellence, decrease TAT and optimize cost

Key Skills: Business Intelligence, Requirement Gathering, OBIEE, Bi Publisher, Data Modeling, ODI, SQL Server, Data

Warehousing, Performance Tuning, Data Analysis, Tableau Developer, Tableau, Data Visualization

Worked on project tracking tools like TortoiseSVN, JIRA for version control and BI object management

Proven skills in administering & ensuring successful project delivery, growing business footprint, increasing customer and stakeholder satisfaction

Knowledge in upgradation & migration between Dev/Test/Prod Environments

Conferred with:

- Customer Centricity Award from Zensar, 2018-2019
- o Customer Centricity for Quarterly Awards during 2018-19 by Zensar Technologies Ltd.
- o Best Performer of the Year Award from Client Herbalife, 2016-2017

Extensive experience in designing, development and implementation of OBIEE and Tableau

### **Work Experience**

- Apps Associates as Lead Consultant Sep 2020 to Till Date
- Zensar Technologies Ltd as Senior Software Engineer Jan 2018 to Dec 2019

Key Result Areas:

Contributed as key member in implementation & upgradation of the project and rendered production support for deployed project till it is stabilized

Mindpool Technologies Private Limited as Software Engineer

Nov 2015 to Dec 2017

Kev Result Areas:

Installed, upgraded & configured database solutions through OBIEE tools; created dashboards, reports and ad hoc queries

Prepared RPD (Physical, BMM and Presentation Layer); steered the execution of security profiles like (Ldap, SQL Provider) in WebLoqic

DRS Dilip Roadlines Private Limited as Software Engineer Jun 2011 to Nov 2015

Key Result Areas:

İdentified business requirements; developed functional requirement document & technical requirement document Analysed Facts, Dimensions, Levels/Hierarchies of Dimensional Modelling; prepared many reports with different Analytics Views (Drill-Down, Pivot Table, Chart, and Tabular with Global and Local Filters) using SSRS

# 1

# **Important**

 Using Free CV Search you have access to featured candidate profiles of Naukri. You can browse through the profiles and email the candidates of your choice directly using the email option provided. To prevent misuse of candidate information, contact details and attached resume of the candidates have been withheld.

#### **Education**

UG: B.Sc (Computers) from Andhra University in 2000

PG: MS/M.Sc(Science) (Computers) from Sikkim Manipal University of Health Medical and Technological Sciences, Gangtok in 2003

^ Back to Top

# IT Skills

Skill Name	Version	Last Used	Experience	
OBIEE11g&12c, ODI				
Data Analysis, Data Modelling				
MS SQL, Oracle SQL, Toad for Oracle				
Tracking System JIRA, Tortoise SVN				
Cherwell, ServiceNow (SNOW)				
OBIEE	11g	2017	4 Year(s) 7 Month(s)	
OBIEE	12c	2020	2 Year(s)	
TABLEAU	10.x,2019	2020	2 Year(s)	

^ Back to Top

# Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English				
Hindi				
Telugu				

^ Back to Top

# **Affirmative Action**

# **Work Authorization**

Category: General Job Type: Permanent

Physically Challenged: No Employment Status: Full time

^ Back to Top

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICICIcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQs - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICIClcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.